<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Underrepresented Group</string>
    <string name="brief_bio">
        \t Any person who works with Computer Graphics or had a Computer Graphics course in college might not be
        unfamiliar with Phong Shading algorithm. Born in 1942 in Hanoi, Vietnam and got an engineering degree in
        France, he then received a Ph.D in University of Utah College of Engineering. Despite being a genius, Phong
        had a short lifespan. He was soon diagnosed with leukemia, a type of blood cancer. He died in 1975, two years
        after receiving his Ph.D.
    </string>

    <string name = "person_early_life">
        \t Phong was born in Hanoi (French Indochina at that time period). Information regarding his early life is not well-known.
    </string>

    <string name = "person_education">
        \t During his early years of education, he attended Lycée Albert Sarraut, a school founded by the French during their
        colonialism in Vietnam. He then moved to Saigon in 1954, where he attended another school named Lycée Jean Jacques Rousseau.
        In 1964, Phong moved to France and ettended Grenoble Institute of technology.
        \n\n
        \t In 1968, he joined  Institut de Recherche en Informatique et en Automatique (then IRIA) as a Computer Scientist, working with operating systems.
        Later in 1971, he joined Utah College of Engineering as a research assistant and received Ph.D from this college in 1973.
    </string>

    <string name = "person_person_accomplishments_1">
        \t Phong\'s greatest contribution to the Computer Science field has been Phong Reflection model. This model allows computers with less computational power during the 70s to
        create a more true-to-life model compared to the flat shading model.
        \n\n
        \t The idea of Phong Reflection model came from an assignment that required Phong and three other students to port a real life object, in this case, a Volswagen Beetle,
        into a computer that enbables user to perceive such object at first sight. That was how Phong Shading came around.
    </string>

    <string name = "person_person_accomplishments_2">
        \t The ability to create such a shading model that brings an object as close to how it appears in real life requires not only knowledge within Computer Science and Math,
        but also Biology, especially how human brain perceives and processes shadows.
    </string>


</resources>